[
    {
        "id": 31,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns the largest of three numbers.",
        "default": "function maxOfThree(a, b, c) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function maxOfThree(a, b, c) {\n  return Math.max(a, b, c);\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns a string made of the first 3 characters of another string.",
        "default": "function firstNChars(str) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function firstNChars(str) {\n  return str.slice(0, 3);\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that checks if a number is even.",
        "default": "function isEven(num) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function isEven(num) {\n  return num % 2 === 0;\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns the minimum number in an array.",
        "default": "function minInArray(arr) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function minInArray(arr) {\n  return Math.min(...arr);\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns a string in uppercase.",
        "default": "function toUpperCase(str) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function toUpperCase(str) {\n  return str.toUpperCase();\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns the length of an array.",
        "default": "function arrayLength(arr) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function arrayLength(arr) {\n  return arr.length;\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns true if a number is exactly 10.",
        "default": "function isTen(num) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function isTen(num) {\n  return num === 10;\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "type": "function",
         "question": "Write a function that returns true if a string starts with 'JS'.",
        "default": "function startsWithJS(str) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function startsWithJS(str) {\n  return str.startsWith('JS');\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns the last 2 characters of a string.",
        "default": "function lastTwoChars(str) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function lastTwoChars(str) {\n  return str.slice(-2);\n}"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "type": "function",
        "question": "Write a function that returns true if a number is divisible by both 2 and 3.",
        "default": "function divisibleByTwoAndThree(num) {\n\n}",
        "solution": "function divisibleByTwoAndThree(num) {\n  return num % 2 === 0 && num % 3 === 0; \n}"
    }
]